Episode 12.4 «Japari Bun Harvesting»
Sorry for gathering you!
What's the matter, Margay?
I thought today was an off day?
We'll help you out if you need it.
Well, you see…
I'd like to ask your assistance in a favor from the owls.
It's rare for them to be so personal. What kind of favor?
We need to provide 100 Japari buns!
More than 200, if possible.
Japari buns~
Hululu, we're not eating...
Ah, is this for Kaban-san's journey?
Huh? Didn't Boss prepare that for her?
Isn't Serval following along? That must be it!
Ah, I see.
Not bringing along her own food… she'll die of starvation.
We need to prepare 200 buns, just about enough to fill this sack!
Can you girls do it?
Got it!
100 buns… that's quite the amount.
But Boss only gives us as much as we need to eat…
About 5-6 buns at the most.
If only there was something we could rely on…
Princess, is there a place for that somewhere in this island?
Well, I heard rumors that there is a place where Boss makes Japari Buns…
Ah! I've also heard that. But no one's ever actually seen it…
It must be that the professor
wants us to «go real quick and do it for us».
Well, it's not like the amount they're eating will change in the future.
It'll be like getting it in advance.
Well, where is it?
Well, they said,
«We're leaving the rest to you. We are busy».
«Let us go, professor. Slurp.»
«Let us go, assistant. Slurp.»
They're dumping it all on us?!
Are those two actually busy?
Hrmm… Let's go ask other Friends!
It's for Serval and Kaban. Let's do our best!
We asked a bunch of Friends, but none of them knew.
Well, they wouldn't know about much outside of their territory…
Hm? Hey, PPP, what's the matter?
Hello! Thanks for your help last time.
Not at all, Kaban-san. We owe it to you as well.
We're glad that you're fine.
Yo, Serval! We're looking for Japari buns.
Huh! Why; what are you girls doing?
It's for when you're going to follow Kaban-
W-Well, we have our reasons…
And so we're looking for where Japari buns are made!
Supposedly there's a place where Boss makes them, but no one knows where it is.
I see. I don't know either…
Kaban-chan, do you have any idea?
I know! When Lucky-san has no more Japari buns to distribute,
it'll go back to fetch some more;
Let's try to follow it!
I see!
You're amazing as usual, Kaban.
Let's go find one now!
Yeah!
I don't really get it, but I'm glad I was able to help out.
Let's also go and have some fun!
Oh yeah, Campo Flicker said she would teach us how to find a place to sleep!
Wanna go?
Yeah!
Boss… Boss…
A Boss with a basket…
He always appears out of nowhere when we're out of Japari buns…
There it is!
Seems, a bunch of Friends have just come to get them.
There's about 2 or 3 buns left.
Aww, I want some too…
Didn't you already eat just now?
Ah! There's no more!
What shall we do…
We didn't think about that, did we…
He's started to move.
Let's follow it!
Urgh… it's actually pretty hard
to walk on rough paths in this body…
Is that so?
Don't push yourself too hard, Emperor.
We can't lose sight of Boss!
Ah! I see something.
There's a hole in the cliff…
Is it a tunnel?
There are other Bosses around the entrance.
A Boss with a basket is entering!
Let's follow it!
H-huh? Why are you obstructing me?
It looks like Boss is angry.
I-I'll move farther away.
What do we do?
Should we force our way through?
But, if we make Boss angry, there'd be nowhere to run.
Kaban-san can talk to Bosses. Should we try and ask her to persuade Boss?
But then, we have to keep secret the fact that Serval is tagging along…
If we say too much, she'll find out.
Yo!
rustle… rustle...
Huh?
Giant-senpai?!
What? Haven't you girls found any Japari buns yet?
No, not yet…
But how on earth did you know?
Mysterious, as always…
Ni-hi-hi
Well, the Bosses won't let us in through the entrance over there…
I see.
How about pretending to be sincerely troubled in front of Lucky Beast?
Pretending to be troubled?
It's not that that thing helps people only.
Boss will support Friends who are troubled about this and that.
Huh.
See ya!
Well, try to do well.
rustle, rustle, rustle...
What was that about?
Somehow, everything Senpai says is usually spot-on...
Let's try it!
Yo, Boss!
Could you let us in
to make it more rockin'?
Uh, well...
«Rocky» not like
cliffs, but I mean
like cool
conquering hardships… or something…
It's no use.
Boss is too scary…
There, there.
I'll go next.
Well, um, Boss.
I need your help.
I, uh…
She's passed out!
No chance,
it's like a blizzard at glance.
There, there.
Gen?
Boss, there's a girl we want to help.
In order to do that, we need Japari buns.
Please, could you let us through?
Thank you so much!
Gen, you're awesome!
Nice one, Gen!
I guess «honesty is the best policy», eh?
There's light coming from the exit,
but it's still pretty dark, huh.
Ow!..
You'll hit your head if you jump in here, Iwabi.
Let's walk slowly.
I can see it now.
What a huge lake.
For a place like this to exist in the park…
There's an island.
Maybe that's where Boss is.
Let's go.
What a mysterious place.
The sunlight through the trees feels nice.
Ah! Look over there!
Japari buns are hanging from the trees!
And there's a lot too.
What could it mean?
Do Japari buns grow on trees?
Ah! Bosses!
They're throwing bunches of Japari buns into the trees and letting them hang.
What are they doing?
It's shiny and pretty.
They left.
Where did they bring it here from?
Now's our chance.
Let's go get the ones here!
You're right. Let's go!
This is…
quite a tough job.
I'm still not good at such precise work yet…
We have to prepare a a little more for those girls.
We don't know if there's anything to eat outside of the island!
If we don't hurry up, Boss will come back.
Heave-ho, heave-ho- heave-ho.
Man, she's fast!
When it comes to Japari buns, Hululu'll work faster…
Amazing. She's collected about 100 all by herself.
Ah! Bosses!
Shoot, they've spotted us!
L-let's make a run for it!
What do we do? More of them are coming!
Eek! They're really furious!
Let's get away by swimming. Jump into the lake!
Hup!
In the end, the water is pretty soothing, huh.
Alright. Let's gather distance.
Gen is fast as always~
Let's go, let's go!
Iwabi is fast as always~
Alright. We've shaken them off.
Let's keep this pace all the way to the exit!
More Bosses coming from the tunnel!
What do we do? There's a bunch of them coming from behind too.
Eek! It's hopeless!
Darn! Is this the end?
Heave-ho, heave-ho, heave-ho, heave-ho…
We're the first to arrive!
What?
What is it? What is it?
Where's the round thing?
Where is it?!
Huh? It seems like we hit something just right now…
You girls are…
I'm Arai-san!
I'm Fennec.
Wow, what is that?
Heheh. It's a «bus-lookalike»!
The Professor gave it to us!
Ah. Bad news, Arai-san.
It seems like we hit a Boss.
I-I-I'm sorry, Boss!
It seems like their body is okay.
But they seem kind of angry. Let's get away.
Heave-ho, heave-ho, heave-ho, heave-ho, heave-ho, heave-ho, heave-ho…
Wow, so fast~
You saved us!
So, what are you two doing here?
A girl who looked kinda like this
said that the thing we're looking for would be somewhere around here…
There was no round thing!
She tricked us!
It must be Giant-senpai…
She saw it all coming, didn't she?..
Man, she's creepy…
Well, we're okay for now, I suppose.
We're okayn't!
There's no round thing!
Now, now.
We got out alright in the end and helped out some Friends.
It's alwrong!
Arai-san's future is in danger!
Thank you all so much for your hard work!
Man, it was scary!
Ahh, we had a nice walk and a nice swim!
Worked up a good sweat!
Why you!.. Now only was there not a round thing, but Boss got angry at us!
It was scary!
Now, now. In comparison to dinosaurs,
Lucky Beast is pretty cute!
Dyna-sore?
Sounds like it was rough!
Wanna eat? It's almost ready!
Yes, yes, we'll eat.
Is this the rumored «cooking»?
Serval-chan cooked most of everything today.
That's right!
Kaban. Make sure to taste-test it.
Let us eat. I'm starving.
Don't you girls have Japari buns? Want some of mine?
No, we have some, just that
there's someone we want to feed.
We're getting ready.
Almost like for the chicks!
Maybe we should have carried them by swallowing them first.
What?! That's an excellent idea!
A very penguin-like way of transport!
Uhehe… I'd like to get to eat that way sometime…
I don't know what you're talking about,
but I think I prefer receiving them normally.
What about Kaban? Where did you go today?
Today, I had Campo Flicker tell me some things.
I learned a lot!
Although sleeping in an anthill may be difficult,
it is importnat to reuse things that already exist as beds.
They're right petrified of Boss…
But this Boss isn't that scary.
Maybe other Bosses would be nice too if they could talk.
By the way, what's the «round thing»?
The Professor asked us to look for it!
It's a surprise.
The journey is a long one.
Ours is a surprise too!
Is that so? Are you girls going to please someone? I can't wait!
It looks like you're all having fun!
Ah, the cooking is ready!
Let's eat!
Cooking, huh. It's been a while. Ni-hi-hi.
Thank you, Serval-chan.
Kaban. Make sure to taste-test it.